notificationresults.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Ploicy

**Privacy Policy  **

We gather but do not link unique and job data

notificationresults.com Privacy Policy

This sheet notify you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal details we receive from users of the Site.

We use your personal details only for providing and giving moral or intellectual benefit the job Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at www.notificationresults.com.

**Information Collection And Use**

Period of time using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally noticeable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally visible information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number.

**Log Data**

Like many site speculator, we collect more details that your browser sends whenever you visit our site log data. This Log Data may include details such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with little amount of data, which may include an unspecified unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to gather more details. You can require your browser to decline all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

**Security  **

The security of your private details is important to us, but recollect that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially supportable means to protect your private details, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy  **

notificationresults.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.
